[
{ "question": "Show me the Wikipedia entry of Bushwick",
  "answer": "Here it is:",
  "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bushwick,_Brooklyn"
},
{ "question": "Show me some Latin restaurants in Bushwick",
  "answer": "Here are some of the highest rated Latin restaurants:",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=Latin+restaurants&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Show me some Chinese restaurants in Bushwick",
  "answer": "Here are some great Chinese restaurants",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=Chinese+restaurants&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Show me some American restaurants in Bushwick",
  "answer": "There are many delicious American restaurants in Bushwick",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=American+restaurants&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Show me some Japanese restaurants in Bushwick",
  "answer": "Here are some of the top Japanese restaurants in Bushwick",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=Japanese+restaurants&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Show me some Italian restaurants in Bushwick",
  "answer": "Here is a list of the best Italian spots in Bushwick",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=Italian+restaurants&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Show me some cafes in Bushwick",
  "answer": "Here are some cafes in Bushwick",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=cafes&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Show me some coffee shops in Bushwick",
  "answer": "Here is a list of the top coffee shops in Bushwick",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=coffee&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Show me some pizza places in Bushwick",
  "answer": "There are a plenty of great pizza places in Bushwick. Here are some",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=pizza&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Show me some ice cream shops in Bushwick",
  "answer": "Here are some of the best rated ice cream shops in Bushwick",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=ice+cream&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Show me the best bars in Bushwick",
  "answer": "Bushwick has a great bar scene. Here are some favorites",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=bars&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Show me the some lounges in Bushwick",
  "answer": "Bushwick has great nightlife. Here are some lounges",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=lounges&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Where can I get good brunch?",
  "answer": "Here are my brunch suggestions in Bushwick",
  "url": "http://freewilliamsburg.com/listings/the-best-brunch-in-williamsburg-greenpoint-and-bushwick"
},
{ "question": "How far is JFK airport from Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Not too far. It is about 25 minutes without traffic",
  "url": "http://open.mapquest.com/embed?hk=12OFnwP"
},
{ "question": "How far is LGA airport from Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Not too far. It is about 25 minutes without traffic.",
  "url": "http://open.mapquest.com/embed?hk=12OHLUh"
},
{ "question": "How do I get to Penn Station from Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Here are the driving directions. Penn Station is about 8 miles away from here. It will take approximately 20 minutes without traffic.",
  "url": "http://www.mapquest.com/embed?hk=1q962yq"
},
{ "question": "How do I get to Grand Central from Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Here are the driving directions. Grand Central Station is about 8 miles away from here. It will take approximately 20 minutes without traffic.",
  "url": "http://www.mapquest.com/embed?hk=1tZyhfe"
},
{ "question": "How do I get to Times Square from Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Here are the driving directions. Times Square is about 8 miles away from here. It will take approximately 17 minutes without traffic.",
  "url": "http://www.mapquest.com/embed?hk=1s6uCM1"
},
{ "question": "How do I get to Chinatown from Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Here are the driving directions. Chinatown is about 6 miles away from here. It will take approximately 18 minutes without traffic.",
  "url": "http://www.mapquest.com/embed?hk=1yquVnj"
},
{ "question": "How do I get to Central Park from Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Here are the driving directions. Central Park is about 8 miles away from here. It will take approximately 22 minutes without traffic.",
  "url": "http://www.mapquest.com/embed?hk=12aKjLF"
},
{ "question": "Is today a good day to walk the Brooklyn Bridge?",
  "answer": "I’m not sure. Let’s check the weather.",
  "url": "http://www.accuweather.com/en/us/bushwick-ny/11221/daily-weather-forecast/2624674"
},
{ "question": "What are some museums I can check out?",
  "answer": "You’re in for a treat. There are many museums near Bushwick",
  "url": "http://www.mapquest.com/embed?hk=12aISwB"
},
{ "question": "What are the newest spots to check out?",
  "answer": "Bushwick Daily is a great source. Let’s take a look at new places.",
  "url": "http://bushwickdaily.com/tag/new-places/"
},
{ "question": "Where can I check out graffiti in Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Here is a map of graffiti around in Bushwick:",
  "url": "http://freewilliamsburg.com/self-guided-bushwick-graffiti-tour/"
},
{ "question": "How should I spend a day in Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Here are my suggestions:",
  "url": "https://www.timeout.com/newyork/art/a-day-in-bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Are there any good shows tonight?",
  "answer": "Check here for some shows in the area:",
  "url": "http://bushwickdaily.com/category/music/"
},
{ "question": "What are the subway stations in Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Here are the subway stops in the area:",
  "url": "http://bushwickdaily.com/2013/02/a-newbies-guide-to-bushwick-subway-stops/"
},
{ "question": "Are there any farmers markets in Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Yes, there is Bushwick Farmers Market. Take a look:",
  "url": "http://www.bushwickfarmersmarket.org/"
},
{ "question": "Are there any flea markets in Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Yes, there is Shwick. Here, take a look:",
  "url": "http://shwick.us/"
},
{ "question": "Where can I rent a bike?",
  "answer": "Here are a few places:",
  "url": "https://www.yelp.com/search?cflt=bikerentals&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY#find_desc=bike+rental&cflt&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick/"
},
{ "question": "Where are the best thrift stores in Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Here are a few places:",
  "url": "http://brokeandchic.com/the-best-places-to-go-thrift-shopping-in-bushwick-brooklyn/"
},
{ "question": "Where are some parks in Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Here are a few parks in the area but here is the most popular:",
  "url": "http://www.bushwickinletpark.org/"
},
{ "question": "Where can I catch a movie?",
  "answer": "I recommend this theater:",
  "url": "http://www.nitehawkcinema.com/"
},
{ "question": "What art galleries are there in the area?",
  "answer": "Here is a list of art galleries and studios:",
  "url": "http://bushwickdaily.com/2014/09/a-newbies-guide-to-the-bushwick-art-scene-select-galleries-studios-who-is-who-and-where-to-submit/"
},
{ "question": "Where should I go shopping?",
  "answer": "I recommend here",
  "url": "http://shopsattheloom.com/"
},
{ "question": "Are there any vegan restaurants in Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Yes, here are some vegan restaurants:",
  "url": "http://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=vegan+restaurants&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "Are there any vegetarian restaurants in Bushwick?",
  "answer": "Yes, here are some:",
  "url": "http://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=vegetarian+restaurants&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY&ns=1#sortby=rating&l=p:NY:New_York:Brooklyn:Bushwick"
},
{ "question": "What are some famous attractions here?",
  "answer": "Here are a few:",
  "url": "http://bushwickdaily.com/2013/03/bushwick-attractions-for-tourists-as-welcomed-by-mayor-bloomberg/"
},
{ "question": "Where can I get the best doughnut?",
  "answer": "Here is a top rated doughnut shop in Bushwick:",
  "url": "http://dunwelldoughnuts.com/"
},
{ "question": "Where can I get the best doughnut?",
  "answer": "Here is a top rated doughnut shop in Bushwick:",
  "url": "http://dunwelldoughnuts.com/"
},
{ "question": "What is the best pizzeria?",
  "answer": "Roberts is a famous and top rated pizzeria in Bushwick.",
  "url": "http://www.zagat.com/r/robertas-new-york"
},
{ "question": "Where are the best happy hours?",
  "answer": "Here are a few local favorites:",
  "url": "http://bushwickdaily.com/2013/10/happy-hour-in-bushwick-where-to-drink-after-work/"
},
{ "question": "Are there any good performances going on?",
  "answer": "Check out the Bushwick Starr for some performances:",
  "url": "http://www.thebushwickstarr.org/"
},
{ "question": "Are there any bowling alleys around here?",
  "answer": "There are a few bowling alleys in this area:",
  "url": "http://www.yelp.com/search?find_desc=bowling+alleys&find_loc=Bushwick%2C+Brooklyn%2C+NY/"
},
{ "question": “What are the best contemporary art galleries around here?”,
  "answer": “Check out these 10 galleries in Bushwick:”,
  "url": "http://www.roberthenrycontemporary.com/press/20141104-nyc-culture-guide-bushwicks-10-best-contemporary-art-galleries/"
},
{ "question": “Are there any speakeasies in Bushwick?”,
  "answer": “There are. But you should try this one:”,
  "url": "http://gothamist.com/2014/02/06/1_knickerbocker.php#photo-1/"
}
{ "question": “Are there any speakeasies in Bushwick?”,
  "answer": “There are. But you should try this one:”,
  "url": "http://gothamist.com/2014/02/06/1_knickerbocker.php#photo-1/"
}

]